## Connor Kai-Ho Lee

connor.lee@yale.edu 626-377-5522

#### **OBJECTIVE**

Highly motivated college student at Yale university interested in gaining experience in social-robotics. Through my organization and communication skills, I can solve problems both independently and collaboratively. I have demonstrated reliable service and worthy contribution to the development of quality products and projects during my previous internships, and I would be a beneficial asset to your team.

#### **EDUCATION**

Yale University, New Haven, CT

2019 - Present

U.S. Citizen

Bachelor of Arts in Cognitive Science (2024)

- Cognitive Science Coursework: Thinking, Mental Lives of Babies and Animals, Mystery of Sleep, Intro to Cognitive Science
- CS Coursework: Intro to Information Systems, Computer Science & the Modern Intellectual Agenda

#### Loyola High School, Los Angeles, CA

2015 - 2019

Highschool Diploma

- Cum Laude
- Loyola Men's Varsity Swim Team Captain (2018-2019)
- USA Swimming Scholastic All-American (2016-2019)

#### **TECHNICAL PROFILE**

#### Programming:

• Python (2 years); HTML (1 year); CSS (1 year); MATLAB (<1 year); Swift (<1 year)

#### Platforms & Systems:

Windows; Mac OSX; Linux

#### Other:

• Microsoft Office Suite; Google's G Suite Adobe Photoshop

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

## Yale Interactive Machines Group, New Haven, CT

Machine Learning Research Assistant

August 2021 - Present

- Collected and analyzed 100+ video hours of people engaging with an interactive system
- Implemented multiple Python scripts utilizing NumPy arrays and pandas data frames to organize and prep data for testing
- Trained various machine learning models (RF, KNN, etc) to determine the best classifier to predict future user engagement

#### Schulte Research, Austin, TX (remote)

Research Intern

January 2021 – April 2021

- Spearheaded research on the new wave of PropTech startup companies by exploring venture capital firms' portfolios
- Acknowledged in Paul Schulte's book The Digital Transformation of Property in Greater China: Finance, 5G, AI, and Blockchain
- Discussed with teammates about the viability of 25+ PropTech companies in terms of business objective, user platform, and practicality of technological tools.
- Prepared a 50-page PowerPoint highlighting eight potentially successful companies' growth, business models, and market strategies

#### LinQuest Corp., Los Angeles, CA (remote)

Finance Intern

- Created 10+ spreadsheets daily for program managers to evaluate budget allocations and analyze costs for upcoming projects
- Used Salesforce to organize completed proposals and company expenditures for accessibility, visibility, and auditing
- Managed weekly COVID-19 business interruption charge reports during the coronavirus pandemic ensuring employee efficiency

### Yale University, New Haven, CT

Men's Swimming and Diving Member

Aug 2019 - Present

- 20 hours a week of training
- 2020 US Olympic Trials qualifier
- 2020 Ivy League Champion
- School record holder in 100 Butterfly and 50 Butterfly

#### Organizations

## Yale Undergraduate Aerospace Association

2021

#### Volunteering

## Loyola Senior Service Project, Los Angeles, CA

2019

Aided teachers at an impoverished LA county elementary school by tutoring students in reading and writing

#### Los Angeles Food Bank, Los Angeles, CA

2016

• Packaged and sorted food items for distribution among underprivileged citizens living in LA County

2016

Baja Build, Tijuana, MX
Built a 2-story house and privy for a homeless woman with a team of 10 classmates and their fathers

# Connor Kai-Ho Lee

connor.lee@yale.edu 626-377-5522

LANGUAGES

English (Native)

**INTERESTS** 

Star Wars, Skateboarding, Movies, Anime, Music, Traveling, LEGO

## REFERENCES

**Jim Henry**, Robert J.H. Kiphuth Head Coach @ Yale Swimming & Diving james.henry@yale.edu

**Paul Schulte**, Founder @ Schulte Research paul@schulte-research.co

U.S. Citizen

# Connor Kai-Ho Lee

connor.lee@yale.edu 626-377-5522 U.S. Citizen